airdna.co 2019-12-17

# Privacy Policy for AirDNA's short-term vacation rental data services.

AirDNA has undergone a full audit under the new GDPR regulations, which came into force on May 25, 2018.

Below we explain when and why we collect personal information about individuals who visit our website or use our products and services, and how we use it. This Privacy Policy may change in the future, so please check this page from time to time to ensure that you are still happy with the agreement outlined below.

If you have any questions about the AirDNA Privacy Policy, please contact AirDNA, 1523 15th St. Suite 200, Denver, CO 80202, USA. You can also email [hello@airdna.co](mailto:hello@airdna.co), or telephone [+1 720 372 2318](tel:+17203722318).

At airdna.co (“AirDNA”, also referred to in this Policy as “we” or “us”), we provide data and analytic services on vacation and short-term rentals (the “Services”). This Privacy Policy describes how we collect information from you in performing our Services, how and when it is used, who we share that information with, and how we keep the information that we collect safe and secure.

This policy is part of our [Terms of Service](https://www.airdna.co/terms). By visiting our website or using our Services, you consent to our use of your personal information in the ways set out in this policy and in our Terms of Service.

If you do not agree to any part of this Privacy Policy, then we cannot provide the Services to you, and you should stop using AirDNA or accessing the AirDNA website. If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement or do not feel that your concerns have been addressed, please [contact us](https://www.airdna.co/contact).

AirDNA requires users of our Services to be at least 18 years of age (or have the permission and supervision of a responsible parent or legal guardian). AirDNA’s website is not designed for use by minors, and AirDNA does not intentionally collect information regarding minors. Therefore, this Policy does not discuss use of our website or Services by minors.

## Information collected or received

You do not have to submit any personal information in order to browse or use AirDNA’s website. Where relevant local regulation permits, AirDNA may share your personal data with selected and relevant counter parties. 

We use technologies such as cookies and web beacons for several purposes, including to help understand how you interact with our website and Services, in order to provide a better experience. You may limit certain tracking by disabling cookies in your web browser. Although AirDNA does not currently respond to “do not track” browser headers, you may opt out of online behavioral ads through this link.

When you register for AirDNA via the sign up page, we collect and store your first name, surname, email and industry. When you get in touch via the contact page, we collect and store your name and email; we also store your company, country of operation and phone number if you chose to provide it. If you launch our live chat function, we ask that you provide your name and email so that we are able to easily identify you, and will store it if you choose to provide it. When you make a purchase, we collect billing or payment information; we may store credit card information and use it for both billing and payment purposes.

We may use the personal information you have provided us to create a profile of your interests and preferences so that we can contact you with information relevant to you. We may make use of additional information about you when it is available from external sources to help us do this effectively.

In providing our Services, we collect property and rental information from various third parties and public sources, which may include personally identifiable information. We want to be clear that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that AirDNA does not own or control, or individuals that AirDNA does not employ or manage. AirDNA does not control the privacy policies of third parties. And AirDNA is not responsible for the privacy or security practices of AirDNA’s users or other websites on the Internet, even those linked to or from the AirDNA website. If you provide your information (including personally identifiable information) to others, different practices may apply to the use or disclosure of the information you provide to them. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

## Using and sharing the information that you provide to us

We will collect from you and store your personally identifiable information only when you expressly provide it to us and only for the reasons set forth in this Policy. We process that information in a variety of ways to provide the best possible services to you and our clients, for example, to make a record of what products or services customers are interested in, streamline communication with customers, make amendments to customer product subscriptions, and carry out any contractual obligations, such as taking payments from customers.

If you wish to withdraw your consent to receive updates and offers, simply click “Unsubscribe” at the bottom of the email. You can also email us on [hello@airdna.co](mailto:hello@airdna.co), or telephone [+1 720 372 2318](tel:+17203722318).

AirDNA may also release your personal information to a third party in the following circumstances: to protect, establish, or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; to comply with a subpoena, court order, legal process, or other legal requirement; or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law, prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, threats to our property, or violations of AirDNA’s Terms of Service.

If you reside in the European Union, please note that the personal data information we obtain from or about you may be transferred, processed and stored outside of the E.U. for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, including in the United States of America.

### Access to Information

We appreciate that you want to control the information that you provide to us and ensure that it is accurate. AirDNA gives you the choice of providing, editing or removing certain information, as well as choice over how we contact you. You may change or correct your AirDNA account information through the website, or by contacting us, and you may unsubscribe from our Services at any time. If you have any problem accessing your profile, or would like to request a copy of your personal information, please contact us. In all cases we will treat requests to access information or change information in accordance with applicable legal requirements.

### Data Security

AirDNA follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once AirDNA receives it. These standards are periodically reviewed and, if necessary, updated or revised. Only authorized personnel have access to personally identifiable information submitted through the website. Such employees are required to maintain the confidentiality of this sensitive data. Unfortunately, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Data Retention

AirDNA will retain your information only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this policy.

If you wish to be deleted entirely from the AirDNA customer database under the GDPR Article 17 “Right to Erasure” (May 2018), email us on [hello@airdna.co](mailto:hello@airdna.co), or telephone [+1 720 372 2318](tel:+17203722318). AirDNA will retain and use your information to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

You may inform us of any changes or requests regarding your personal data, and in accordance with our obligations under applicable data protection law, we will update or delete your personal data accordingly.

## Privacy Policy Changes

We may update this policy from time to time. If we believe that the changes are material, we will let you know by doing one (or more) of the following: (1) posting the changes on our website, or (2) sending you an email or message about the changes. That way you can decide whether you want to continue using our Services. Changes will be effective upon the posting of the changes. You are responsible for reviewing and becoming familiar with any changes. Your use of the website or our Services following the changes constitutes your acceptance of the updated policy.
